bestdealinsurance.co.uk 2007-12-21

# Best Deal Insurance - Privacy Policy

All data submitted to Best Deal Insurance Services Ltd on this site is secured using Verisign.

##  Best Deal Insurance Services Ltd Takes Your Privacy Seriously

Last update to policy: 29th August 2007

We are Best Deal Insurance Services Limited, trading as Best Deal Insurance and our registered address is 3rd Floor, Avon House, Tithe Barn Road, Wellingborough, Northants, NN8 1DH, United Kingdom. Best Deal Insurance Services Ltd takes the privacy of its customers data very seriously.The statement below covers the site www.BestDealInsurance.co.uk. 

Please read the following policy to understand how we will treat your personal data when you use our site. If this policy changes then we will let you know via our homepage but we assure you that we only use your data as specified here and for our legitimate business reasons. 

## When do we collect data?

We can collect data on you from a variety of different sources. 

  * When you take a quote or purchase products or services from the site; 
  * When you become a subscriber; 
  * When you speak to our customer services personnel; 
  * Via explicit data capture measures, for example by entering competitions and completing surveys; 
  * Via implicit data capture measures such as studying which pages you read the most and the use of cookies; 
  * In any of the above cases the data we collect could be personal data. 

## What do we do with your personal information?

When you buy anything via the site, we may need to collect information about you to process the transaction, fulfill your order and provide you with the services you expect. This information may include, but is not limited to, details such as your name, your address and your email address. 

Unless we have your express consent we will only disclose personal data to third parties if this is required for the purpose of completing your transaction with us. This is of course subject to the proviso that we may disclose your data to certain permitted third parties, such as members of our own group, our own professional advisers who are bound by confidentiality codes, mortgage lenders and insurance companies, to help process and administer any policy or loan that you require and when we are legally obliged to disclose your data. 

Best Deal Insurance Services Ltd retains and uses your personal information to provide you with the best online e-commerce experience by providing you with a personalised service and to give you details of offers which we think will be of interest to you. We may also use the information to process any transactions you undertake with us and for internal administration and analysis. 

We do not sell, rent or trade your personal information to third parties for marketing purposes without your express consent. 

For any of the above purposes we may send your information internationally including to countries outside the EEA. Some of these jurisdictions offer differing levels of protection of personal information, not all of which may be as high as the UK. 

We do not send random marketing emails to personal email addresses (spam).

## Data

In the UK we operate and are registered in accordance with applicable data protection legislation.  
Best Deal Insurance Services Ltd conforms with the requirements of the Data Protection Act, 1998. 

## Consent

By disclosing your personal information to us using this website or over the telephone, you consent to the collection, storage and processing of your personal information by Best Deal Insurance Services Ltd in the manner set out in this Privacy Policy. Some information and e-mails sent to Best Deal Insurance Services Ltd may be used as testimonials but no e-mail address or contact details will be displayed. 

## Change/Modify Details

To change your e-mail address details send an e-mail with your correct details to: [info@bestdealinsurance.co.uk](mailto:info@bestdealinsurance.co.uk)

If you need to Modify or Change your personal details after you have made a purchase on the site please e-mail us at [info@bestdealinsurance.co.uk](mailto:info@bestdealinsurance.co.uk) as soon as possible.

## Contact

If you have any questions or concerns about the information we hold about you, you can also email us at [info@bestdealinsurance.co.uk](mailto:info@bestdealinsurance.co.uk) or alternatively call us on Freephone 08000 324455
